<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Wildwood Bugle</title>
    <description>News and views from your favorite park.
</description>
    <link>http://wildwoodbugle.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://wildwoodbugle.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 10:17:34 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 10:17:34 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sharks Spotted in Paradise Falls Pond?</title>
        <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;leadart&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/paradisefallsshark.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PARADISE FALLS — For years now, hikers have reported seeing shark-like fish in the deeper waters of Wildwood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The earliest claim came about five years ago. A resident living near the edge of the park apparently flushed a pet shark down the toilet, after it grew too large to keep in its tank. The baby shark eventually found its way into the creek that flows through the canyon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But a lack of evidence has left us only to speculate, until last week when the &lt;em&gt;Bugle&lt;/em&gt; received a major tip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While hiking with her family on June 5, Erica Wamboldt snapped this picture of what appears to be a shark fin in the pond beneath Paradise Falls pond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether this oceanic predator has truly made its way into the Wildwood ecosystem is yet to be seen.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 01:43:59 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://wildwoodbugle.com/wildlife/2018/06/12/paradise-falls-shark.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wildwoodbugle.com/wildlife/2018/06/12/paradise-falls-shark.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Wildlife</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Scientists Expect a Big Year for Fluffins</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of Wildwood’s rarest treasures is the elusive California fluffin. Despite their blue feathers, these creatures are crafty hiders that utilize the same camouflage that chameleons use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a winter of heavy rain the chance of spotting a fluffin nearly doubles, according to the research of wildlife specialist Dr. Zedediah Moonridge. The fluffins are particularly unique in the fact that they are attracted to the scent of oxybenzone, the active ingredient in most sunscreens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last summer, signs of these gentle creatures were spotted by hikers soared. This could be attributed to not only the heavy rainfall, but also to the decrease in trail trash and increase in sunscreen use by hikers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although this last winter did not provide much rain, there was enough to promote the growth of wild gourds, lemonberries and cactus fruits, which happen to be just a few of the fluffins favorite sñacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Needless to say, the locals and scientists alike are hopeful for another fluffin filled summer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 01:43:59 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://wildwoodbugle.com/wildlife/2018/06/05/fluffins.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wildwoodbugle.com/wildlife/2018/06/05/fluffins.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Wildlife</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wildwood Wizard: Hero or Menace?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The so-called “Wildwood Wizard”: Is his purpose one of justice or trouble? It’s a debate that’s divided Wildwood locals for years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;Bugle&lt;/em&gt; has followed the story of the silver staffed sage since the beginning. To date, there has never been any actual cause for alarm related to the wizard’s activities in the park.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Past, unconfirmed reports include casting mind control spells and stealing the voices of hikers — and conjuring frightful images of flying dragons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unbeknownst to most, the Wildwood Wizard has been spotted performing good deeds as well: Helping little ducklings across rattlesnake infested fields, using his magic to help cacti bloom in the drought and even reportedly deterred Horseman from entering a residential area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“He’s a crook who needs to be put behind bars,” declares Agnus Jenkins, a local resident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Others like avid hiker Harold Toppinton thinks differently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“He’s the guardian that Wildwood deserves, his harmless tricks are only used to teach us,” he told this reporter while hiking near Lizard Rock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems it’s up to the individual whether this character is good or evil.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 00:43:59 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://wildwoodbugle.com/magic/2017/12/18/wizard-hero-menace.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wildwoodbugle.com/magic/2017/12/18/wizard-hero-menace.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Magic</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Giant Spider Found Living Under Park Shed</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Rabbit populations declined significantly year with the recent introduction of a new species of giant spider discovered in the park this year, ‎&lt;em&gt;Hogna persulensis&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This species is closely related to the California wolf spider, except it is a darker shade of brown and is reportedly several times larger. Scientists have found molted skin measuring more than two feet in length.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Several of these spiders had reportedly created a living space under a shed in the park a year ago, but it appears they have since moved out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Every morning I walk Rex through the park, but I haven’t seen any since last August, not even a web,” said local dog walker George Jenkins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For several months, there were no signs of the spiders, but this reporter kept digging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Volunteers were recently seen clearing up a section of trial near Meadows Cave of large string like webbing stretched across the trial. The trail was unusually crowded that morning, as dozens of people worked to discard the debris.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It remains to be seen whether the spiders have increased their range in the park.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 01:43:59 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://wildwoodbugle.com/wildlife/2017/08/19/spider-shed.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wildwoodbugle.com/wildlife/2017/08/19/spider-shed.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Wildlife</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brave Heroes Slay Dragon, Mysterious Wildwood Wizard Escapes</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For the past week, the &lt;em&gt;Bugle&lt;/em&gt; has been flooded with reports of a large flying creature in Wildwood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The creature is thought to be a dragon, apparently summoned by the Wildwood Wizard so he could reverse the flow of the creek and poison the park with wastewater. The situation was dire enough that the Wildwood Council of Animals mustered the aid of a band of local heroes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the help of the Five Sword of Wildwood, the so-called Knights of Wildwood defeated the dragon, afterward setting off to discover the identity the Wildwood Wizard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But thanks to his ability to temporarily possess the minds of mortals, the wizard was able to elude capture. For now, at least, his true identity and motives remain unknown.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 01:43:59 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://wildwoodbugle.com/magic/2017/07/20/dragon-wizard.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wildwoodbugle.com/magic/2017/07/20/dragon-wizard.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Magic</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ancient Fossils Discovered in Creekbed</title>
        <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;leadart&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mermaidfossil.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It appears as though the myths about a half-human, half-fish creature have been finally put to rest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a creekside deep in the canyon, the children of a local camp have discovered the ancient remains of what appears to be a mermaid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dozens of bones were recovered from the dig site, however, the most important piece of all, the skull, was nowhere to be found.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When local scientists heard from a reporter about the findings, they jumped at the opportunity to research the specimen. Yet, shortly after the bones were unearthed, the samples went missing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world may have to wait longer yet for definitive proof of the existence of mermaids.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 01:43:59 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://wildwoodbugle.com/anthroplogy/2016/07/07/mermaid-fossil.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wildwoodbugle.com/anthroplogy/2016/07/07/mermaid-fossil.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Anthroplogy</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AD: Have you seen this chicken?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;PAID ADVERTISEMENT:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;leadart&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/goldenchicken.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2016 01:43:59 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://wildwoodbugle.com/neighborhood/2016/06/25/missing-chicken.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wildwoodbugle.com/neighborhood/2016/06/25/missing-chicken.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Neighborhood</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Squirrels in Space Launch from Teepee</title>
        <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;leadart&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/spacesquirrelship.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THE TEEPEE — This week marked an historic event in sciuridae space exploration when a team of Wildwood squirrels successfully launched a rocket from the Teepee Space Center (a bush next to the drinking fountain) in the early morning hours Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Led by Captain Chester T. Nuterman, the crew of the &lt;em&gt;Acorn&lt;/em&gt; is expected to land on the moon by next week, perhaps next month, according to Heironimus Bushytail, leader of the launch group’s calculations department.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After several failed launches earlier in the week, Mission Control celebrated exuberantly after they learned via a series of cups connected by a string that the &lt;em&gt;Acorn&lt;/em&gt; had flown above the clouds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/spacesquirrelcrash.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not just a giant leap for squirrel-kind, but for the budding Wildwood Space Program. We here at the Bugle look forward to reporting on the continued progress of the mission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UPDATE Oct. 15, 2015 — The Bugle has learned that the squirrel ship, the &lt;em&gt;Acorn&lt;/em&gt; has landed on the moon. Although the flight took longer than expected, the team is nonetheless declared a mission accomplished.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/spacesquirrelmoon.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 01:43:59 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://wildwoodbugle.com/wildlife/2015/08/27/space-squirrels.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wildwoodbugle.com/wildlife/2015/08/27/space-squirrels.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Wildlife</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Local Mischief Makers Identified as Gnomes!</title>
        <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;leadart&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/gnometent.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For weeks, the &lt;em&gt;Bugle&lt;/em&gt; has received reports that small, almost insignificant, pieces of property have been going missing around the area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“My favorite gardening equipment went missing from my backyard recently, two small trowels and a tiny shovel,” said one resident, who did not give her name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another neighbor said that he found his favorite pair of jean shorts outside with a rectangular hole cut right out of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Now I need to find a new pair of shorts!” the man said. He was too embarrassed to give his name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even the local summer camp had some of their snacks stolen from Meadows Cave.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The culprits are believed to be Gnomes, short magical creatures no taller than a couple feet, often “gnown” for harmless mischief and thievery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To prevent further mayhem, wanted signs were posted at trail heads to warn hikers and residents.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2014 01:43:59 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://wildwoodbugle.com/magic/2014/08/10/gnomes.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wildwoodbugle.com/magic/2014/08/10/gnomes.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Magic</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hikers Spot Strange 'Horseman' in Wildwood</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Two hikers reported seeing a “monster” in Wildwood Regional Park on Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brendan Picklestraub and Greta von Stassleberry were out walking the trails before Fourth of July fireworks when they spotted what they described as a man with the head of a horse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I didn’t get a good look at it, but it was about six feet tall and had a mane like a horse and big creepy eyes,” Stroganoff said. “This was no deer.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Park rangers and guests have dubbed the creature “The Horseman” since sightings of the animal began last month. Most of the sightings, including Thursday’s report, took place deep inside the canyon, passed Lizard Rock, the highest point in Wildwood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, I saw the monster. He was galloping through a patch of poison oak like it was nothing,” said Wildwood Camp Director Oak, who takes dozens of kids into the canyon twice a week. “It made this gnarly sound, man. It sounded like a horse!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Park rangers have made little progress in tracking the animal in Wildwood’s rugged terrain. Biotechnology giant Amgen has also joined in the search. The company stated the animal was part of its local pharmaceutical experiments, but it went rogue after a lab accident.
“We are making every effort to retrieve the experiment,” an Amgen spokesman said.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 01:43:59 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://wildwoodbugle.com/wildlife/2012/07/05/horseman.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wildwoodbugle.com/wildlife/2012/07/05/horseman.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Wildlife</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
