<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.4.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-02-25T15:30:12-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Your awesome title</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Half man, half horse spotted in Wildwood</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/animals/2012/07/04/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Half man, half horse spotted in Wildwood" /><published>2012-07-04T12:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2012-07-04T12:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/animals/2012/07/04/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/animals/2012/07/04/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;Two hikers reported seeing a “monster” in Wildwood Regional Park on Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Victor Stroganoff and Greta von Stassleberry were out walking the trails before Fourth of July fireworks when they spotted what they described as a man with the head of a horse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I didn’t get a good look at it, but it was about six feet tall and had a mane like a horse and big creepy eyes,” Stroganoff said. “This was no deer.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Park rangers and guests have dubbed the creature “The Horseman” since sightings of the animal began last month. Most of the sightings, including Thursday’s report, took place deep inside the canyon, past Lizard Rock, the highest point in Wildwood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, I saw the monster. He was galloping through a patch of poison oak like it was nothing,” said Wildwood Camp Director Oak, who takes dozens of kids into the canyon twice a week. “It made this gnarly sound, man. It sounded like a horse!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Park rangers have made little progress in tracking the animal in Wildwood’s rugged terrain. Biotechnology giant Amgen has also joined in the search. The company stated the animal was part of its local pharmaceutical experiments, but it went rogue after a lab accident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We are making every effort to retrieve the experiment,” an Amgen spokesman said.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Two hikers reported seeing a “monster” in Wildwood Regional Park on Thursday.</summary></entry></feed>